[
  {
      "title": "1980's History"
  },
  {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "Which space shuttle tragically exploded shortly after liftoff in 1986?",
      "answer": "Challenger"
  },
  {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Which disease was first identified in 1981 and became a global epidemic?",
      "answer": "AIDS (Acquired Immunodeficiency Syndrome)"
  },
  {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "Which major nuclear disaster occurred in 1986?",
      "answer": "Chernobyl disaster"
  },
  {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "Which iconic music television network was launched in 1981?",
      "answer": "MTV (Music Television)"
  },
  {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What computer company released the Macintosh in 1984?",
      "answer": "Apple"
  },
  {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Which actor became President of the United States in 1981?",
      "answer": "Ronald Reagan"
  },
  {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "Which global pop star was assassinated in 1980 in New York City?",
      "answer": "John Lennon"
  },
  {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Which country won the FIFA World Cup in 1986?",
      "answer": "Argentina"
  },
  {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "Which technology company introduced the Game Boy in 1989?",
      "answer": "Nintendo"
  },
  {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Which country did Iraq invade in 1980, sparking an eight-year war?",
      "answer": "Iran"
  }
]
